You will not escape my curse!
God help me!
Alps! Wait for me to hear from paper clip jugs!
Alps retreat!
Don't leave anyone alive!
Oh right!
The fate of all of you will be worse!
We've destroyed their headquarters, Olof, we have to go.
This is just the beginning, they will pay for every blood they shed.
We'll make it pay, Olof. We'll pay together, but not now... Not now.
We're pulling back!
What headquarters is this Osman Bey!
From whom did you get permission and you set up headquarters!
by God!
I don't get permission from anyone for gas in the way of truth.
If you don't know me, ask the person next to you.
He knows me well.
You're being unfair, Osman Bey.
I give you full credit.
Hunter, reach the headquarters with our soldiers.
May you come to the rescue of those who are broken for the sake of a dreamer.
No...
We don't need anyone's help
You break the peace between the two states!
You go and raid them!
You will pay for them!
We pay whatever the price is, wherever you want, whenever you want.
Mr. Turgut!
You stay.
He's leaving, my sultan, won't he catch up?
It only arrives in the morning, when everyone perish.
You see, right?
What, His Excellency, Sultan?
Osman's arrogance!
Kibri will defeat Osman!
Choose your rank now!
Are you with Osman or with me?
No, nowhere, no news from the alps at the door.
He left Yenişehir in the morning and never came back.
Something has definitely happened to them!
Open your mouth for good, Ayşe Hatun.
Shouldn't they have fled to Oba?
No Ülgen, her daughter ran away, would Bengi ever sit idle?
By now he had raided our mansion.
Aha, look at yours there.
They told me to prepare the stick at the moment.
Does the girl whose daughter ran away ever come to the market?
There is a business in this business... There is a business in this business.
If you have a heart, come to me.
Who are you and what are you? I will find you, I will find you!
Get in front of me, you coward!
Subasi is just yours.
You get your water out.
Don't think about it.
Good, let's go to Yenişehir too.
Those who can't see us may be suspicious.
Well, my newly engaged man, let's go and stand at our counter.
Couldn't they escape!
Wow what happened to us!
- Well, if Alçiçek is here...
Where is Aktemur?
Ülgen, let's check this girl's mouth.
Ayşe Hatun, Ülgen Hatun.
What do you want from me?
Mr. Alçiçek Aktemur-
- My mother is coming!
Don't let him see you.
You should not mention that name to me again. That matter is over!
What do you say, Alçiçek?
I will marry Bayındır. You stay away from me.
Walk...
I don't understand anything, what's going on?
What will happen, it is obvious that he has returned from the Alçiçek road.
Ah Aktemur ah!
I went on a road
Or?
- I'm going to kidnap Alçiçek.
Did you say to run away?
- He said.
While leaving the fort.
She is angry with heart... If she loves you enough to leave her mother and father behind.
Don't worry, go do what you have to, I'm behind you.
Then I won't make you wait, the crooked trees in the pine grove wait for me there.
Good luck, Aktemur, be cautious.
There is no Sister Aktemur, you should inform Malhun soon.
Let's go where Aktemur said
Alps! Get the horses ready and we'll go.
I will come with you, I will not leave you alone.
Come on, Ulgen, come on.
Alps!
We will bury our martyrs, who will set off soon, in Yenişehir.
Osman Bey is coming!
Catapults.
There's a lot of work in these...
There is good work.
are you okay?
- I am good.
honey...
honey.
My Bala is my valiant girl.
are you okay?
- I'm fine Osman, but...
They burned down everywhere.
All around... the Alps...
You didn't trust your brain, is that it?
Come here... Come here! When we turn our backs, they raid the headquarters.
Now get out of my way!
I've been standing behind you for all these years.
But your anger has blinded you, Osman Bey!
At the very first mistake, you hit it and you lose it.
Turgut Bey was right.
- Fall down!
Storm.
Call the gentlemen, I'll collect the sofa
The command is my lord.
They broke our arm but we can't stop
Now they're going to want to hit us on the head.
Orhan!
- Sir.
Arrive in Karacahisar with your brother and lure all the gentlemen.
You will take them all and come to Yenişehir.
- It's your command, sir.
honey.
You go with the alps.
I'm going to drop by someone and come over.
Thank you sir.
Come on alps.
Oh braves...
O Allah, grant us to take revenge on the oppressors and traitors, amen.
Prosper and send word to Olof. Let them come to listen to my new orders.
I'm going to have more to do with Olof than I thought.
Are you really going to give Marmaracik to Olof, my sultan?
That fool thinks so, but I'm not going to give a piece of land.
When I'm done with Osman, I'm done with Olof.
What will your next move be for Osman, sir?
I will create a great hell for Osman, the hell of loneliness.
His friends, people and even his family will not stand by him.
I will blow the wind of absence in Yenişehir.
The people of Osman's brain will starve.
They will fall for me.
They will turn their back on Osman.
Those who turn their backs on Osman will be with me.
Valide sultans will take care of the whole Yenişehir.
Count the warehouses, too, so that no gaps are left.
We have entered a path, but may God bless our end.
Amen sir, amen.
This intruder... Now you raid our property?
Cut!
Get out.
You put our case halfway through.
They killed our Alps.
Only you knew where the headquarters was.
You put us in the middle of nowhere.
And now, should I know this from you?
You told me that as if you didn't even know it.
Even if our paths are one, let's not cross each other, Osman Bey.
Our path is not the same when one becomes a servant to the Sultan.
You don't know what you said and now you accuse him of treason?
You're completely blind-
- I'm not rolling my eyes!
I know you haven't shrunk enough to say headquarters.
But you're small enough to turn around.
They dared and attacked because it wasn't you.
I leaned on you, I knew you as a mountain.
But you, you weren't even a hill.
You hurt me the most.
What did you do to me?
I'm not a blunt knife, Osman, if you sharpen that much, I'll cut it too, of course.
I said to the one who sharpened himself against me for a property!
Let this be a lesson to me.
do you know what you did?
You changed what you set out with what you found on the way.
Do you know how many losses I have when I walk behind you?
How many wounds are on my body, how many precious things have I lost in my hand!
Few of my followers are alive.
I buried my woman with her baby in her womb, Osman Bey!
I buried my brothers and sisters!
Have we given these losses to return from the road for a fortress?
Fortress...
If the case does not reach its goal, then all the losses are in vain!
You still say citadel.
What fortress? Can't you see I'm the ruler of Inegol.
The issue is different.
Osman... Now walk and see if you can walk to Köprühisar...
Osman, this move must have driven him crazy, Olof.
We broke Osman's feet.
Soon, very soon, I will break his neck as well.
Ismihan became what the sultan wanted.
I think he was satisfied.
- And ours?
Will it be what we want too?
Marmaracik is ours now.
My brother Frodi is right. What if Ismihan Sultan does not give Marmaracik to us?
olof.
Ismihan sultan wants to meet you.
Is it different...
Other...
The issue is different.
You want more, you are not satisfied with what you have.
Your heart is full of greed for property.
Look at you, look at this arrogance!
You put me in this situation, are you going to complain about Turgut that you have turned into now?
Have you forgotten the injustice you have done, Osman Bey?
Of course I will give the castle to Öktem! Certainly...
They will leave if I do not give them property.
They pull away.
But you, you were my pillar.
I knew you differently.
But...
for a property
I never knew you would switch sides.
I do not change sides for neither property nor property.
Make your final decision.
Choose your side.
You are not what I swear.
Get out of the pen now, Osman Bey.
Inegol...
- Inegol.
it is not yours.
This is not bloodless...
I always fought, I always took the lead.
I endured the fitna, but...
but those behind me have always fallen for these tricks.
I always fought.
Now you too will fight... Against me.
Two days, you will leave this place!
We will give our lives
but if you want our homeland
We don't give, Osman...
Then I'll take both!
There are horse marks on both sides.
Sisters! Open your eyes!
Let's not put a place we didn't look!
We will turn every place upside down, Ayşe Hatun, may your heart be at ease.
We will find a trace.
There is no returning to Yenişehir without finding a trace!
Where are you son?
Where are you?
What is this?
Ulgen...
- These earrings
Don't you have Alçiçek?
Well if it came here... I'm totally confused
Did you understand anything from this?
I don't know Ulgen, I don't know.
All I know is that Alçiçek has eaten my son's head.
Seven.
Ayse Hatun.
Say!
This is the horse of my lord Aktemur
My God, protect me, O Lord!
Aktemur.
Call...
Search everywhere! Find and search!
Find my ulgen son.
We will find it.
Ah!
My daughter...
What is this madness?
Are you thinking of Aktemur again?
No, why should I think about the man who left me behind, mother?
I think about what I will do.
Good for you to listen to your mother.
That boy has no heart to run away.
His love was a lie, my daughter.
You listen to your mother, don't worry about the rest, emi?
I've had my share, mother.
Other than that, whatever you say.
At that time, I say, let's not delay this naive thing, let's do it right away.
Sir, what is this situation, are you going to the sofa?
What if we go to the sofa
I don't know how to look at Osman Bey's face.
You didn't do anything wrong, a thousand people want a girl, one person gets it.
There is nothing to be offended about in that.
That's right.
But we didn't do well, we turned Osman Bey out of the door.
What would we do when there is a huge Ismihan sultan?
Were we going to listen to Osman Bey?
You did the right thing, and behind you is Ismihan Sultan.
Alflower is she alright?
Is there consent?
I talked to him and he has consent to marry Bayındır.
Good, Aybars...
Let's go so we don't be late.
You will wait, gentlemen.
What would we wait for?
Are we not allowed on the other sofa?
What could be the reason for the Alps?
Osman Bey sees it as unsuitable.
If there is a problem, the Alps will accompany you until the Yenişehir gate.
Selamun aleykum.
- Aleykumselam.
Gentlemen, our wedding was a divan.
Of course this will come at a cost.
The cost of this was also a decrease.
Our path is more arduous than before.
But the conquests will continue.
We will continue to march on the enemy.
We will never bow to the oppressors.
But if anyone wants to cross the threshold of the sofa
he will know the greasy rope around his neck.
on the sofa without putting his head under his arm.
No one will attempt to cross the threshold!
This is my last warning, this is the last chance for anyone who wants to return.
No reason will be asked of those who want to go.
But if anyone wants to come, our door is always open.
He who does not risk death will not walk on this road! Come on guys!
Osman Bey gave salut, why do you stand?
He also warned us
He said, 'Hey, the one who turns from the road will lose both his highness and his principality.
Alp, a person who is not a gentleman has no right to carry a pusat.
Give!
There was to smash it with my embers...
Here you are.
that holds us responsible for the expedition, not the victory
I open the divan in the ninety-nine names of Almighty Allah.
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim.
"Bismillahirrahmanirrahim."
Of course, you heard what happened to our headquarters in preparation for the conquest.
We heard the black news, Osman Bey.
But that's not what you needed to hear!
All you needed to hear was the rumor of conquest.
Sir, you keep your conquests a secret...
Who is the one who demolished the headquarters?
I'll take his head when I find out.
Who is the attacker?
The attacker is Olof.
No attack, no betrayal, is strong enough to stop us.
That's why I assembled the sofa.
We will put everything that was burned in its place as soon as possible.
We are ready to do whatever it takes, sir.
Blood, blood, life.
Thank you, thank you.
What would Osman Bey Ismihan Sultan say about this situation?
You were going to give me land, my sultan.
How many years ago did your ancestors come to Constantinople?
Two centuries?
three centuries?
Despite all these years of service, the land that Rome did not give
What makes you think you can take it from me so easily?
That's not the point, I did what you said, now it's your turn, sultan.
You will give me the land you promised, the Marmaracik fortress!
Here too!
Lord Olof, are you so keen on dying?
I will keep my promise...
you are who i am! You will not forget, Commander Olof!
Do not...
If I give you a piece of land now, Osman will take it back immediately.
Good thing he tries, I'll crush him under those walls.
Not your own desires! You will do what I want...
First, Osman will disappear.
When Osman gets the news, he goes out to look for his nephew Aktemur.
And you're going to lure him into the biggest trap.
To the death trap.
- Don't worry, sultan.
I've already prepared my move.
My Sultan Turgut Bey is coming.
Anyone who is curious about Ismihan Sultan's opinion should follow him.
Why did you cross the threshold, Mr. Şahin?
I ask simply to understand the situation we will take.
If you have any doubt, the oily rope is on our neck, Osman Bey.
Thanks...
Otherwise...
What is spoken on the sofa stays on the other sofa.
The conquest of Köprühisar was over.
All the preparations were destroyed!
But...
Now is the time to conquer
They will not anticipate that we will be ready in a short time.
Let them know about Köprühisar.
They won't even be able to imagine that we're walking.
Alps.
- Sir.
You will cut down trees even in the dark of night.
You will continue to build the catapults by torchlight.
It will be prepared from the Alps thesis.
Blacksmiths will continue to beat the pusats without blinking an eye.
And you will bring the war equipment.
They cut off our beard, we will cut off their heads.
I hope soon, sir.
The other divan is finished, you should make your preparations from your thesis.
The pusats you will bring will be the key to the conquest.
Mr. Osman!
Aktemur...
What happened to Aktemur?
- It's not there, sir!
My Bey went to kidnap Alçiçek, and never came back.
I went to the place he promised, he has a horse, but he does not.
Osman, I have no children!
What do you say, Ayşe lady? Why would you do such a thing without asking me?
Boran, send the Cerkutays to the place where the thesis Ayşe is talking about.
Let him start looking for traces.
Let the Alps get ready, our range will be elsewhere.
The command is my lord.
Her Majesty the Valide Sultan.
Then, my Valide Sultan, I will immediately start the preparations for the wedding.
Start, of course, start so that you can walk the path.
Walk so that you can reach vusla, Bayindir.
Heads up, my Valide Sultan.
Yes, Mr. Turgut, what brought you here without even informing?
He did not choose the right one that I said Gardaş.
On the contrary, he wants İnegöl under my control.
I'm here, Mr. Turgut! Osman does not rule where I am!
Does he want all his property to be taken with a single edict?
What does this Osman Bey want?
Arrogance...
Unfortunately, there was truth in what you said.
Arrogance Osman has blinded the brain.
Whatever he wants, he wants from him.
He took us behind him and lined you up before him.
He made many conquests.
Now he wants to be sentenced with cruelty.
Didn't you shed blood for İnegöl, Mr. Turgut?
You shed your sentence like great gentlemen.
You even dared to turn your back on us.
Osman fought the so-called oppression, and now he is one of the oppressors.
While I am here, it is forbidden to persecute them, Turgut Bey.
If you take my side, you will be provided with as many soldiers and commuters as you wish.
You will always feel the presence of the Valide Sultan behind you.
I didn't believe what you said before but I saw it with my own eyes
I have no place in those who have no loyalty to me.
I'm naive...
Valide Sultan is with you.
Osman will fall into our hands when he thinks he has come to you.
Your turn will come too.
But first I'm going to kill your uncle.
And when I get what I want, I will give your blood to Odin.
You will not reach your goal, dog breed!
Did you throw the bait?
- And how...
First we made it even harder for them to find traces that would confuse them so they wouldn't suspect.
But all traces will lead them to the same place.
Osman's tomb.
Today we will fight like it is our last day!
We will kill Osman and those around him!
Stay on top of it.
Don't worry, I'll continue to be very nice to him.
Let your axes be your sharp Odin companion! Let's go!
very nice Martha
Send me a ball of each of these.
Of course, Bengi Hatun, when you look at the fabrics you have chosen
It is clear that you understand from the fabric.
Bengi Hatun knows the best of everything.
Oh dear, it means the wrong done to her has been done to us.
Let him give the best of everything he chooses.
Welcome, Mr. Bayindir.
Certainly.
Good to meet you, Mr. Bayındır, I would call you too.
No need to delay the wedding.
Let your mouth eat honey, Bengi lady.
I will come after our Valide Sultan.
We say let's have the wedding tomorrow.
While the litter is gone
must not delay.
The way of reason is, I will talk to Mr. Öktem and you can start your preparations.
Hussein!
- Sir.
We have a bridal shower tomorrow.
It's your command, sir.
Speaking of trash, I couldn't see you around. What did you do to Aktemur?
I didn't do anything but...
Obviously, someone acted before me and removed the trash in the middle.
Well, I didn't get my hands dirty for nothing.
What can I say, I am a beloved servant of Allah.
Hatun, you can write whatever Bengi chick chooses on my account.
He doesn't! We see our own business.
Just do your part.... Groom!
What would you do?
What do you smell, do you think it's food, let the smell come.
Not every trace you left behind, Gürbüz alp.
Some traces are not visible.
Can this be a job! Are you playing games with me!
Osman Bey also gave me this meczubu!
Coming... Coming!
So, you have other skills besides eating food.
If you only knew what other talents I have.
Selamunaleykum guards
- Aleykumselam.
Nothing came of the traces that went since Cerkutay Alp.
It means we are on the right track.
All traces point to the devotees.
You continue along this road...
I'll go and tell my boss.
Look at me! Give me that apple!
Come here give that apple! Give me my apple! I'll burn you, I'll burn you!
Gurbuz, come on.
Anyway, I'll find you.
One of Osman's brains, Konur would like to see you.
Let it come.
What is the reason for you to come before us, bent like this, Osman's alp?
It is waking up from the sleep of years of heedlessness, my sultan.
I am not Osman's alp.
I was a skillful commander of Ulu Selçuk.
So now?
Now I am a man fired by sentence labor.
We're not going to accept everyone who's been fired.
Who wants you to accept my sultan
I came here to ask forgiveness from my state and then to see what I deserve.
What is the treatment he deserves, Mr. Hunter?
Take all you have forty falakas.
- False.
While I was affiliated with the state, I went after a master and betrayed my office.
What I deserve is execution.
- He...
You came here to kill you, right?
It is.
The price of betrayal can only be paid with life.
But you
You will pay with the service.
I will do whatever you want, my sultan.
You will already
What is my duty?
They will think that you destroyed us.
But we will not stumble, the conquest will continue.
As the cause of God makes our hearts tremble
we will continue to shake the world.
Don't fall for yogis!
Our goal is clear.
Our target is Köprühisar.
Our current headquarters is very close to Marmaracık.
Is it for action?
This place will make our conquest easier.
It is both hidden and overt.
If we are this close to Marmaracık, will we inform Öktem Bey?
Let's complete a headquarters, then we will release it if necessary.
Thank you sir.
We said that we would say on the sofa that he already makes his preparations!
We have no secrets from anyone.
When the catapults are ready, we will hit even harder than before!
I hope sir.
- I hope so, sir.
Sir, what about Aktemur?
Aktemur...
- Sir!
Cerkutay
We found Aktemur brain trace, they keep it in the ascetics.
Are you sure?
Traces are tricky, sir, but they all show Pious.
Alps get ready, we'll go get Aktemur.
The face of a child of mine did not smile.
O Lord, forgive my son, O Lord.
Amine.
My Ayşe, you will meet your son with the permission of Allah.
You don't.
Oh, Osman Bey will not put Aktemur in the hands of those rascals.
They're sure to come.
They will come.
Thanks.
Don't say you didn't hear
Tomorrow evening at Marmaracik Fortress with Bayındır Bey
Öktem's daughter, Alçiçek, is born.
Sentence Yenişehir is invited.
Don't, Lowflower!
He burned my daughter's head.
My Ayşe, calm down.
You're all here huh babes.
I also came for good news.
But obviously...
you got the news.
- We got it, Bengi lady.
We got it, good luck!
I hope you, as a mother, will not regret this decision.
May God not make him regret it, of course, but I don't see anything to regret.
Or are you offended because we didn't give Alçiçek to you?
Bengi chick, whatever you want to say
Do not keep us busy for nothing.
I understand that you are offended, but don't be offended, babes.
If my Alçiçek is beautiful, is it a crime if there are many people who want it?
A thousand people want a girl, one person takes it.
Isn't that right, Ayşe Hatun?
Is Aktemur also invisible, ashamed and unable to go out on the street?
Bengi Hatun is Aktemur Subaşı.
He does not even have time to scratch his head, he is on duty.
You should not worry about my boy, if not today, he will forget tomorrow.
Of course he forgets.
Have to forget.
Anyway, please convey my regards to Osman.
We are waiting for you all at our wedding.
My Ayşe!
My Ayşe, let me love your eyes, calm down.
He's here to show off.
Let me find a child
I know I will tell you wait for me.
I'll hold back now, but I'll hold back hard.
But when that day comes, do not stand in front of me!
Sir, there are soldiers guarding all around.
There are too many of them, sir.
We will water our other pusats with the blood of kufr.
We found their lair.
Now we're going to cut off their heads.
Come on God! God is right!
Attack! Kill them all!
Come on, come on...
You're looking for your niece, right?
I get what I'm looking for!
All you get today is Aktemur's corpse!
You won't be able to see him either.
I will take Aktemur and I will take your life too!
Attack!
Come on now! Come!
Cerkutay!
Baysungur.
Osman!
I came to kill you!
I'm here too, so as not to spill the blood of the alps on the ground!
I will kill you with them.
Come on, come on!
orhan.
Masallah!
"Oh right!"
Oh right!
Oh my god!
Oh God!
- Oh God!
"Oh right!"
I say we should test Avcı Bey Konur.
That's how we assign it.
Show your trick.
You are adept.
You will be both my guard and my squire in an equal position to the hunter.
Go now.
Can we trust this, my sultan?
I will make moves that will blow Osman apart.
It disperses... It knows very well that I am the branch to cling to.
Both Turgut and Konur are just the beginning, Avcı Bey.
This location is very close.
I keep those I trust close to me.
I keep the ones I don't trust closer to me.
Don't take your eyes off this Konur.
Until we're sure it's us.
It is your command, my sultan.
Olof! We will not succeed!
Back off!
Olof, I took the head of one of you today
I'll take your heads tomorrow!
Mashallah, mashallah to my valiants.
Sons... You're welcome to come.
Mashallah, mashallah to you, your heart is as strong as your wrist.
As long as you stand shoulder to shoulder like this, by Allah's leave, no one can stand before us.
"Goodbye, sir."
Boran brother, nothing will happen to you, nothing will happen to you
Is this scar worth it to you? Are you okay my guardian?
Sir Boran! Sir!
Bro!
My lord is coming, my lord is coming, are you okay, my guardian? are you okay shhh...
Boran, guard
- Sir
Just hold on.
- I'm fine, sir.
Hold on, get ready quickly, we'll go to Yenişehir.