They are the spoils of the fortress, Turgut Bey.
Brother, sir, do you think the fortress
who will you give it to?
Marmaracik... the most...
It suits Turgut Bey.
Do you think we are entitled, Cerkutay?
Will he find someone better than you, sir?
This is your right.
Thanks.
Thank you, Cerkutay.
Hey mashallah, mashallah!
Forty-one time!
This fortress is as empty as my name.
If Osman Bey could take these for himself...
My Turgut Bey!
He gives them to you too, it's your right.
And this place is up to me.
Before Osman Bey came,
what to yourself
Can you share it, Mr. Bayındır?
Where is Osman Bey?
I don't know where Osman Bey is.
When it will come, God knows.
But what are you doing?
Fine!
Then let's enlarge this barn with the alps.
We have many horses.
The barn is small.
No no.
Whatever we have to do, we do.
You go back to your workbench.
Don't lose your money.
Lets.
Is there no man to stand at the counter?
He has no business here.
Get back to your own business.
You have no duty here, Mr. Bayindir.
We have a lot of duties, gentlemen.
Let's act, valiants!
What are you after?
Where is Osman Bey?
I'll be back at my workbench, but...
If you start a business against me,
I will destroy the world on your head.
Lets.
Thank God, my sons
Karaca left for Hisar.
Even if both are one,
it makes me feel comfortable.
Brother takes the burden of brother, of course.
Don't be left behind, either.
They take good care of each other.
How are the preparations?
We loaded the supplies into the car, Malhun Hatun.
We have no shortcomings, thank goodness.
Alps, be on your guard.
The order is yours, Malhun Hatun.
So black
What do you think, Malhun Hatun?
Has the longing for a child started already?
I think of Osman Bey.
He summoned us
he was not in Marmaracik.
He didn't tell anyone where he was.
I was wondering so.
Once upon a time, my father used to say:
even for a breath
In this world where we cannot rule,
You will never be a renegade.
Are the survivors here?
Are the secrets here?
Now you can be the ayan.
Osman Bey!
Selamunaleyküm, sir.
I'm sorry.
Mashallah my valiant!
Robust.
Let's say if the task is complete.
All right, sir.
Now is the time.
Marmaracık opened the door of conquest.
Now,
We will conquer Köprühisar.
Sir, shoot and let's shoot.
Let's break it.
We are always behind you.
Are you behind us?
stagnant water turns into swamp.
But running water is not polluted.
We will be floods of enthusiasm and march on them.
You say now.
What's the weather like in Köprühisar?
Where do you get all these vaccines?
Sir, a horse cannot pass without barley.
Backless Cherry, the enemy cannot break.
Since the map is there,
You have important things to tell me.
Yes, sir.
All in all!
You should look at this Turgut Bey.
You think, on the infidel
walks alone, shoots alone.
If it wasn't for me, inside the walls
Could they enter, Hussein?
They couldn't get in, sir.
They couldn't go in.
But from now on they see.
My name is--
Will Bayındır be in trouble?
Alps!
Treat the pusats!
Who are you, what do you want?
What we want is to agree with you.
But for that we have to stop.
Are you a jinn or a jinn?
I don't know the copy.
What would I agree with you for?
I'll take you to Olof.
First of all,
Let's see the face under that mask.
Yenişehir,
elegant fabric maker, Marta Hatun, huh.
Phrygian
My name is Phrygian.
Was that demon you?
Olof's boy?
er?
What would Olof want to deal with me?
You talk to him.
On top of all the things I know,
a face under the mask has also been added.
Don't say that I'm doing something wrong,
I will burn you all.
I know a lot too.
For example, that you stole gold from Olof,
Mr. Bayindir.
As you know,
as i know,
it can lead you to death.
But,
He called you alive.
Make up your mind now, Bayindir.
Either I will kill you here,
or we'll go to Olof together.
While you have the opportunity,
since you didn't kill me,
I mean you have to.
Fine.
Let's go to Olof Effendi, let's see.
What did he say?
So, the conquest of Marmaracik
ravaged them, heh.
Their hearts tremble with fear.
But these odors also increase the precautions.
to the emperor,
They have written letters and are waiting for support.
They are afraid.
After Bilecik,
how we marched on İnegöl,
now too,
They know that we will march to Köprühisar.
What is the task, you say.
They were getting blacksmiths from the villages.
To repair the walls.
By taking the workers away from their jobs,
They dig a trench.
They also increased patrols.
Marcus!
What is this outfit?
Osman!
Attack!
You know what to do.
disperse!
I'll go now, sir.
No, with me
You will come to Marmaracik.
Kuffar's fortress
When I made the Turkish homeland,
you'll see what it is.
Lets.
The command is my lord.
the hardest part
It is to eat without contaminating haram.
Let's go back to our city,
Let me fill my stomach like this.
Lets.
Lowflower!
Any news from the Alps?
Has Osman Bey returned to Yenişehir?
No, dad.
He did not come at night.
Our Alps are still eyes.
Osman does not stop, he runs water under the straw.
That's how he does his job.
You just sit here and wait for him,
that I will gas.
Bayindir is not there either.
These two would do well without us, but...
This silence is not a good omen.
What job has Osman done so far?
it was for our good, Mr. Öktem?
Let's see what trouble it will cause us again.
Is there a destur, sir?
Subaşı Aktemur wants to see you.
Here you go.
Selamun aleykum.
And aleykum salam.
Lower your head.
Just say it, Subasi.
I bring you Osman Bey's greetings.
Mr. Osman,
awaits you in Marmaracik Fortress.
Marmaracik?
Marmaracik,
It is the property of the non-Turk.
Osman Bey conquered Marmaracik.
In the evening, he arranges a wedding for the masters of the sentence.
He awaits you in his new property.
Thanks.
Leave!
stealing my gold
You killed my men, Bayindir.
If I counted you as my enemy,
I couldn't miss.
That ax was stuck in your head.
Be sure.
I know everything you do.
Gold was also a common property.
Even if you owned it
it was not to benefit anyone else.
Eh!
Just say,
why did you call me here?
I want
deal with you.
against Osman.
to act together.
Olof lord.
Why should I help you?
Who are you?
Well, who are you,
I'm going to sell the huge Osman Bey to you?
Choose the truth.
Be on my side.
Or together with Osman,
you lose too.
By my temperament,
I will not stand on the side to be defeated.
Never tire yourself out.
Bring.
These golds are for you.
With that little thing?
will you fool me?
My treasure,
up to the sea.
These,
just a drop.
Don't ever tire your jaw for nothing.
I am next to Osman Bey,
a thousand times that
I win in conquest.
His booty is abundant, alhamdulillah.
Osman's spoils
Do you believe he will give it to you?
He is using you.
your life, your property,
For Osman to take Marmaracik,
you revealed.
So what will he do?
Who do you think he will give Marmaracık to?
This is the issue between us.
Well, with this issue,
you have no interest.
Don't worry for nothing, girl.
Fine.
We said, we said he to your offer.
What will I gain?
Half of my treasure.
But not just here.
in Constantinople,
I will make you a partner in my treasure.
Osman Bey is very important.
But,
Gold is also very important.
So what I'm saying is,
this is such a moment
It is not a matter to be decided.
give me a little time,
let me think.
I'll let you know my decision tonight.
Think.
Think, but...
If you try to sell us
My ax won't miss this time.
Don't forget this either.
olof lord,
me like this again, bare sword,
you will find it difficult.
If your wrist is enough for my hundred horses,
you do what you say.
Take this.
Let him put on the blindfold, come on.
Come on, take it, come on.
This Bayindir's job is easy.
Osman!
He must have a fault.
When I find him, I'll finish him off.
Everyone around Osman,
Think of it as a flourish.
If we plant a seed of jealousy among them,
Yenişehir resolves itself.
your biggest weapon
you got it talking again, darling
no mortal,
cannot stand against your intelligence.
We'll take a thousand like you.
This fortress, leading to your sentence
I hope it will open the way.
Whoever is skilled in other wars,
be her property.
Is there anyone better than me?
Chasing gas for years,
you run, Turgut.
Whoever has watered this land with his blood,
property is also his right.
To Marmaracik Fortress,
Grant us to judge properly.
Estagfurullah.
Who gave you this right?
Osman Bey, did he say, take this fortress, it is yours?
Then what do you say to yourself?
Masallah,
The throne suits you well, Turgut Bey.
But don't get too established.
You know, we're nomads.
We have no inclination, Boran Gardaş.
He'll sit on my Obama's post
There's no time, you know.
Osman Bey, I hope,
gives you dominion of the fort.
Thanks.
God knows, of course.
We'll see, guard.
Do you see, Mr. Öktem?
You, Marmaracik
You used to say that we will take it with Osman Bey.
While you're sitting in the room
Osman does not take a breath.
If he did such a secret job,
there is one he knows.
Let's go to Marmaracık,
we'll find out, what is it?
What will happen?
He calls to intimidate with his power.
Is your wound healed, Subaşı?
Depends on which wound you ask.
Not every wound heals, Alçiçek Hatun.
Are you hurt a lot?
Hello there.
And aleykum salam.
No, where is this, Mr. Öktem,
to the mail?
Osman Bey invited him to Marmaracık.
We go there.
Don't you know?
None.
Nobody said anything to us.
Subasi!
Do you know why we weren't called?
I have no knowledge.
I am in charge of calling Öktem Bey.
Lowflower!
Come this again.
I've got my eye on you, Alflower.
You name it accordingly.
Well, since.
You have a nice way.
Thanks!
You too, Mr.
Wow Osman Bey, wow!
So he takes the fort with me,
then you ignore me
You can set up a wedding without us.
Is there such a world, Huseyin?
No, sir.
Hisar, whose right is it?
We paved the way for conquest.
What happens if you don't give the castle to the one who paved the way?
Chest chest of gold came out,
They didn't even give our share.
late to the counter,
The Merchant is Bayindir, they said.
These are the cardigan of conquest,
they only suit themselves.
that cardigan they put on,
If I don't tear it apart
They shouldn't call me Bayındır Bey either.
What shall we do, sir?
Since they do not deem us worthy,
burning this earth under their feet,
I will make it hell!
You should be thankful you're alive,
why are you pouting your face?
I look at what you've done to my fortress,
tragedy.
But like any tragedy,
this too will end in blood.
The blood that flows will be your blood.
Look at those banners.
We do not hang it anywhere we do not water it with blood.
Be careful, the blood that sheds is not yours.
And look at these brave men!
They are the ones who run to death laughing.
Cantacuzenos,
don't forget.
Osman Bey, who sent you to Konstantini,
take care of your lands on the way.
Because we're going to come and get them all.
I suggest the same to you,
I will take back everything that belongs to us.
Even more.
We'll see, Your Royal Highness, we'll see.
We'll see, Turgut Bey.
My Osman Bey will come!
Selamun aleykum.
And aleykum salam.
Oh my god!
It is these flags that make the country home.
Hallelujah.
You have equipped everything.
All of you, this is your happy day
welcome to the wedding.
Alps!
Let's meet your guardian, Gürbüz Alp.
Mr. Turgut.
Welcome, Gürbüz Gardaş.
Welcome, guardian.
Like the interior of Marmaracik,
outside is ready too, Osman Bey.
He sweated a lot, valiant ones.
The ladies worked hard too, mashallah.
Thank you, thank you.
Welcome, Gurbuz.
Thank you.
Where were you on duty, guard?
You'll hear when the time comes.
Thanks.
Your secret is just as big as you, everyone.
Let's see, how many arrows will you shoot?
I'll blow your head off, your molasses will spill.
Then when you fall to the ground,
we will be on the same level.
Oh my god!
Where is Mr. Bayindir?
When you don't know when you will come,
I looked at himself to divide the booty.
So I said, go to work.
But evening comes, of course.
You did it wrong.
Without taking the booty from the place of conquest,
No one is sent.
Thank you, Osman Bey.
you're right.
Welcome, sir.
Mashallah, the market is full.
Things go well.
Don't talk, get out.
Lets!
The man builds a foal in his castle,
the market works.
from his seat,
wins his coin by clicking.
When you say let's go to the fort,
come on, Bayindir.
But hold on...
the day will come, the time will turn.
Now it's my turn.
Come on we said
I said hey to Olof's offer,
what the hell are you going to eat?
Repentance astaghfurullah,
repentance astaghfurullah.
Go over there, write what I say.
Lets!
Come on, Hussein!
The sun of Al-i Selcuk,
Sultana.
Just say, what is your exposure?
come one day,
We knew you'd get this place.
Is this a white day or a black day?
Is our coming salvation for you?
or persecution?
Is the day white or black,
you will show.
No.
your soul too
your property and your faith.
it is entrusted to me.
None will be harmed.
You will live freely.
What about taxes?
We heard you dropped them too.
The prosperity of our domination,
you heard too.
Don't worry, it will all fall.
You were ahead that day.
Will you be the ruler of the fort?
I haven't decided yet.
Everyone will know when the time comes.
Cerkutay!
I can't hear, you know!
Hear--
hey, hey.
I know.
I can't hear!
I know, I know.
You do not hear.
Good thing you don't, if you did,
What my Osman Bey said.
Would you stop here?
I'm deaf but...
I'm listening to you.
Tell me, pour it out.
What did he say?
No.
Why can't I tell a man who doesn't hear?
But I have heard such things!
You burned, Cerkutay, you burned!
What did he say?
Did he say about me?
sir?
What did he say, Ülgen Hatun?
Don't crack me up.
What, Cerkutay?
You hear it, you!
So you tricked me, huh?
So you played me!
I ate you!
Don't run away, come.
Don't run away!
Come, don't run away, Cerkutay!
I'll paralyze you!
Good luck with your conquest, sir.
May you exist, Malhun, may you exist.
Marmaracik takes us to our destination
one step closer.
Thanks to you, we got closer, Osman.
Without stopping for a moment, without rest,
You run towards the target.
Your job is too hard.
Just say, how are the children?
Orhan and Alaeddin,
I went to Karacahisar.
Fatma and Halime,
they are with chicks in the mansion.
What about the situation in Yenişehir?
This Phrygian chick,
any news from him?
Not for now, sir.
But the fall of his mask is near.
Hopefully.
Hopefully, he will be too.
Sir,
Who will you give Marmaracik to?
Do you have a name in mind?
Won't you tell me too, my Osman?
When the time comes, everyone
He will know, Malhun.
Is there a destur, my sultan?
Come, Hunter.
My Valide Sultan, Bayındır Bey,
He sent news from Yenişehir.
Read what he wrote, Mr. Bayındır.
The sun of Al-i Selcuk,
I am Valide Sultan.
Read.
Osman Bey is out of the principality.
Unity of the informal state,
has been threatened.
including Constantinople,
meddling in internal affairs
bring us all kinds of trouble
causes pain.
As it is not enough, by making conquests
gets stronger day by day.
At best, the power of the extreme is the power of Al-i Selçuk.
stolen from his power.
My Valide Sultan, whose power makes the world tremble,
come, see and see your power,
crush the questioners.
Your weak servant is Bayindir.
While we struggle to exist here,
Osman uses this as an opportunity.
that we feed with our hands,
if he betrays,
fate,
it is obvious.
that we feed with our hands,
with our feet,
we crush
I have this power.
I will not stop using it.
Hunter,
Prepare your best warriors.
We are going to Yenişehir.
What are we going to do, my sultan?
We will destroy the rebels.
Or kneel down
they will declare their allegiance to us,
or
with my very dear bird,
They will share the same fate.
Destur!
Mr. Osman!
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim.
Selamun aleykum.
And aleykum salam.
Have a good evening.
Marmaracik Fortress,
it wasn't just a property for us.
to our land,
It was the home of those who wanted to spread strife.
But
We dismantled them all.
For that reason,
our wedding table today,
We do it on our own property.
To my Lord, who showed us today,
thank you.
Amine!
Here you are.
Congratulations on your new property, Osman Bey.
But we are not offended.
In such a conquest,
We would like to be with you.
Mr. Oktem,
Every conquest has a secret.
Sometimes this secret
it becomes the key to the conquest.
Thanks.
Gentlemen!
because we did not invite you to conquer,
do not be offended.
We will have many more conquests.
If not today,
Tomorrow we will strike the neck of the infidel together.
Our banner together
we will move forward.
Hopefully!
Hopefully.
May you exist!
Huh, Kantakouzenos?
How are you?
Do they host well?
As you said, Osman Bey,
account of what you've done to me
I will ask you.
If not today,
tomorrow.
For Kantakouzenos
You put poison, didn't you?
Have fun with you, prince.
Eat it.
I know.
But I also know how to take revenge.
You say we won't stop, Osman Bey, huh?
We will not stop.
It is not fit for us to stand still, Mr. Öktem.
We will continue with new conquests.
Good good.
Now you have made our hearts, Osman Bey.
Thank you, thank you.
What a secretive chick you are, Malhun Hatun.
We came, we asked, we did but
You gave a secret, you did not give a secret.
But I'm taken, a little.
Are we enemies?
Why this secrecy?
Estagfurullah, Bengi Hatun.
State secrets are not extorted.
Our attitude is not unique to you.
Bala Hatun,
you were also in the conquest, huh?
Yeah, yeah.
Mashallah, Bala Hatun.
Doesn't stop for a moment, after her,
you run from battle to battle.
We hear about their victories, we are proud.
Estagfurullah.
It is the victory of our sisters, not ours.
lowflower,
one day you will come to our drills.
I would love to, Bala Hatun.
Selamun aleykum.
Aleykum salam.
Enjoy your meal.
You brought joy, my Sheikh.
I found pleasure, Osman Bey.
your conquest,
Congratulations, Osman Bey.
Be there, be there.
a
O my God, the owner of the properties!
You give the property to whom you will,
You can take the property from whomever you wish.
He humiliates whom He wills,
you bless what you wish.
No, it's in your hands.
No doubt,
You are all-powerful.
on your way,
fighting valiants,
make a saint.
Amine.
In this holy cause,
make us always victorious.
Amine.
Here you are my Sheikh, you are welcome.
Thanks.
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim.
Mr. Osman,
An unclaimed property is like a windless banner.
Who will dominate,
won't you say?
I will say.
Sure, I will say.
But the owner of the property
I will explain tomorrow.
Come on, let's.
Enjoy your meal.
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim.
Thanks.
Our sword is like a shield, but.
Repentance astaghfurullah,
Check out the moves.
Gee!
Eat.
Rather.
We do not eat an animal that is slaughtered without basmala.
You know.
we eat.
It's okay.
You made the right decision.
Our Union
It will bring the end of Osman.
I'm not the guy to deal with infidelity.
Yav, I didn't like you very much either.
Get the news.
However, Osman Bey misled me a lot.
He did me a big mistake.
one who sacrifices,
me,
He couldn't keep up with her.
Me too,
I have no choice but to deal with you.
Osman was wrong.
He mistook the real queen as a pawn.
But being with us
when he knocked it down
He will face the bitter truth.
He will face.
The price of being ungrateful to me,
the state will see it by waking up from its dream.
Never forget what Osman did to you.
Keep your anger alive.
hold that
While destroying Osman,
you will need.
You should never worry about it.
When I make a promise, I keep it.
We'll get on well with you, lord Olof.
And we'll get along very well.
Give the sherbets, Ulgen Hatun.
Mom, stop!
Not a lot.
You can distract my mother a little bit.
Girl, what are you saying?
Your mother eats me raw.
Lowflower!
Take sherbet, Subasi.
Don't get up.
My mother will see.
Tomorrow morning, when the sun is high,
Let's meet by the tree we plowed low.
Alçiçek Hatun,
what does this mean?
Buy sherbet.
Well, Bengi Hatun?
You're a beautiful girl too, mashallah.
Alçiçek has taken your beauty from you.
Dont forget.
I will wait.
Oh my eyes are dazzled!
How can this shine bright, like the moon, mashallah!
Ulgen Hatun.
Get out.
Alps!
Let's pull the pusats.
The command is my lord.
Goodbye, sir.
Come on, guards.
Come on bismillah!
Oh my god!
May you exist, valiants.
O throne,
tell me.
How many brave hearts have you ripped out?
You destroyed the family.
O throne!
Talk.
Talk Talk.
How many states have you been to hell?
Don't touch me.
Don't come in front of me.
Don't try to set me up.
Do not!
Or....
I said don't let anyone in.
Has the throne already bent its back, Osman?
I'm afraid.
I'm afraid, Sheikh.
I'm so afraid.
You should be afraid already.
If I were a gentleman too,
I was also very scared, I would have exploded.
My liver would be purulent.
The throne will be my grave.
I'll eat it with the ground.
Before,
domination of his own soul.
You are now a gentleman.
You are the master of your beautiful soul.
nice brain,
of Alp,
You are the lord of the merchant.
you have judged your own soul.
Or the soul of the people?
Or your men
endless desires?
They'll want booty.
They will want a position.
They'll want supplies.
They will want order, they will want peace.
They will want it and they will want it.
If you give,
what a good
If you don't...
If I don't,
I will be the worst.
Because of that,
Bey is always alone, Osman Bey.
You look from the outside
There are many servants with him.
However,
aspiring to be chief,
consent to be alone
willing to show.
What is loneliness, my Sheikh?
What is loneliness?
They will die for you,
the day comes,
becomes your worst enemy.
Your spouse, whom you lay your head on the same pillow,
makes an alliance with your enemy.
You are the child you tremble,
the day comes,
to get the lordship,
calls you to the battlefield.
And,
nice test, my Osman.
What is the cure, my Sheikh?
Bey's devil will be great.
To get rid of this mortal enemy,
you will be awake.
How can I be?
You will not be mistaken.
How will I not fall, my Sheikh?
How can I not fall?
Opening your heart's eyes.
How will he be?
your nights,
You will spend it with contemplation and dhikr.
Morning prayer is not enough.
You will make your tahajjud.
You will keep the sunnah fasts.
Everyone,
while giving one
You will give a thousand.
You will erase the ornament of the world from your heart.
You will not hurt Tawhid.
Always reciting the Qur'an,
If you light up your night and day,
you stay awake.
When you're awake,
your eyes are opened.
As your heart opens,
when you speak,
when you see,
when you think,
divine manifestation to you,
there will be a torrential downpour.
Your subjects, who see these states of you,
gradually comes to pass.
However,
Every rose has thorns, Bey Osman.
My Yigit Osman!
This will be your test.
The main thing is that from that test
Isn't it successful?
Allah saves us from trials
May he grant us victory, my Sheikh.
Amine.
Masallah!
Mashallah, mashallah!
Sir!
This Olof sounds very uncanny to me, though.
You with a brain like that bird,
Do you question my judgment?
Estagfurullah, sir.
I, so that no harm will come to you.
The real harm to me comes from Osman.
Marma--
In the conquest of Marmaracik,
Didn't I put my life in the middle?
Leave my life, my property
Didn't I put it in the middle?
What did Osman do?
That pintail Turgut,
brought it up to us.
You know best, sir.
I know.
I know, sure.
When trying to go to the conquest,
"Come, Bayindir, to help."
When the conquest is over and the naive is set,
"Come on, Bayindir, to your counter."
Such ungratefulness,
but someone like Osman Bey,
befits a monument of arrogance.
But stop you
Stop.
I deleted them all, all of them.
From Osman to Turgut,
until Öktem.
Now unite with Olof.
I will do what he wants,
and he will make his gold a ladder for my feet.
With that ladder
I will ride on Osman's top.
He used Bayındır and took the fortress.
But toya did not call Bayındır.
See, take your step accordingly, sir.
I see, babe.
I see, but I don't understand.
Why Bayındır
doesn't he call us?
He took the fort, he was done with Bayındır.
Now to you and to the other gentlemen,
intimidates, shows his power.
Let's see who will give the castle to whom?
Marmaracik,
on our route of conquest,
stretches out like a ram.
If we are not cautious,
they will take this place away from us.
What does the measure say, Osman Bey?
We will not stop.
If we stop
here, their swords
We'll stretch it out.
But if we walk
at that time,
to their attacks,
We will fight with our bronze hearts.
We will take Köprühisar.
Sir,
don't you have to stop?
They are on the alert now.
They think so too.
After Bilecik, on İnegöl
how we walked
After Marmaracik,
Over Köprühisar
They think we're going to walk.
they recruit soldiers from the villages,
strengthen the walls.
What is your move, Osman Bey?
We'll pretend to stop.
But in our secret preparations
we will continue.
they are our move
When you think we won't
We will strike them out of their complacency.
But still,
It will not be as easy as Marmaracik.
Who has seen our business easily, sir?
Call the gentlemen.
I will explain the judge of Marmaracik.
Then from the thesis
We will begin the preparations for the conquest.
Orhan!
Sir.
Summon Commander Remus.
The command is my lord.
If the conquest had called us,
I would have hope.
To give it to us. But,
it seems that
The fortress will belong to Turgut Bey.
That's why he doesn't call you!
Hisar was your right.
If you had joined the conquest,
would have to give it to you.
But now go again
He will give it to Turgut Bey.
You teach right.
You always say the right thing,
I can't put it.
If you had listened to me
now fly bey, not Osman Bey,
you would be
Come on, come on.
We'll be late for the party.
Lets.
Doesn't Alçiçek go to the market?
He has a job in the room, he will come when his job is done.
Mr. Baydir!
Are you inside?
Here you go, Shamil Alp.
Selamun aleykum.
aleykumselam
No, Shamil Alp?
My Osman Bey sets up a sofa.
He orders all the gentlemen to respond.
The word of our lord is above our heads.
You go.
We'll be there before anyone else, I hope.
Why are you closing shop this time?
Shamil Alp,
you're in the shop!
The shop is open, not closed.
hey.
I saw the truth.
who stand against the truth,
I also saw how their heads fell.
can i trust you
If I couldn't trust
I already got your head.
Now you will go to the emperor.
Kantakouzenos, sole heir to the throne
You will say that you have
for trusting me
I am grateful, Osman Bey.
But...
If Kantakouzenos is in business with Olof,
Living is the last thing I want.
I know.
So just the news
I'll send you to pass it on.
You are loyal to the emperor.
If you stay here
It does not put Kantakouzenos alive.
I hope the Emperor
falling into the trap of these traitors,
He will not continue to enmity with you any longer.
You,
you are a good friend.
You are an honorable commander.
Have a nice trip.
Call the gentlemen.
The command is my lord.
We can't leave Remus in Osman's hands.
In Yenişehir, in Marmaracık,
You will have eyes everywhere.
You will follow him.
What does Osman want from Remus?
us it,
that merchant
The lord will tell.
Thanks to him,
We will know every step Osman takes.
If we keep Bayındır's gold abundant,
continues to work for us.
To bring the end of Osman,
we can sacrifice a few golds, darling.
And when we're done with that merchant,
We will get our gold back.
Selamun aleykum.
And aleykum salam.
Come, Gürbüz Alp, come.
You can get your shot here, come on.
you teach,
you step on my veins, Baysungur.
Here you go, Gürbüz Gardaş.
No food. So there is, up to me.
Cerkutay is insatiable, you will get used to it.
You get used to it.
Come, Ulgen sister, come.
Ulgen sister, come.
Come, Gürbüz Alp is very hungry.
God bless your hands.
Enjoy your meal.
Ulgen Hatun!
I am here, me.
I don't hear.
Eat, eat. Enjoy your meal.
daddy.
I'm hungry Ülgen Hatun, I'm hungry.
Ulgen Hatun!
Put it, put it, put it, put it, put it.
Let him count what he ate all the time,
Cerkutay Alp.
Sister, fill some more.
This is not enough for the cavity of my tooth.
It's a little bit, it's not enough for him
Put a little more, a little more.
Ye my Cerkutay, eat.
Also, when you reach Köprühisar,
You will be longing for Yenişehir's vaccine.
Look, come on.
Osman Bey is in Köprühisar
He will give you a task.
Well...
The hiccups got hold of me, that hiccup--
Enjoy your meal.
We hurt Ülgen Hatun a lot.
Leave.
You leave.
The strength of my wrist is from my heart
come, you said.
You'll be strong enough to eat that much, of course.
Eat less, less.
Leave.
You leave.
Hey guards!
There is enough food for all of you.
Come on, come on.
Eat your vaccine as soon as possible,
A sofa will be set up.
Cerkutay, come on.
Share some, share.
You leave.
What a Köprühisar, man!
Where did this come from now?
Oh my unfortunate head!
Sir.
Sir!
The sofa is up.
Why do we go down?
Since the sofa is above,
why do you follow me?
Hush, okay.
You wait here.
Don't follow me.
What happens, Ülgen Hatun, are you crying?
What will happen?
Cerkutay
Oh!
Osman Bey,
now too,
He will take Köprühisar.
Well, what's good, what's wrong with that?
There's nothing wrong with that, of course.
The Turkish homeland expands.
They widen,
Osman Bey,
Cerkutay too,
He was going to assign him to Köprühisar.
The joy of the host to go.
Oh, I do not say for myself,
In the absence of Cerkutay,
Who will eat all that food?
From him.
Mr. Osman!
I knew it wouldn't stop, but...
I didn't know its range.
Now I learned that too.
Köprühisar, huh?
No, Mr. Bayindir?
The sofa is not on this side.
So was Essahtan.
However, Osman Bey,
He built such a large mansion that
where is the footpath, where is the sofa,
we got it all mixed up.
Especially guards, just say a word,
Which side is the sofa on?
The Divan is on this side, Bayındır Bey.
Here you go.
Cheers, guards.
Osman Bey walks to Köprühisar.
Have Tez go to Olof and let him know.
Mr. Osman!
Selamun aleykum.
And aleykum salam.
Here you are.
We are not from victory,
responsible for the expedition,
In the ninety-nine names of Almighty Allah,
I open the sofa.
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim.
Mr. Baydir!
When he first came to the sofa,
You brought a chest of gold.
Hey, sir.
I brought a chest of gold when he sold it.
bring it.
These,
From the conquest of Marmaracik
your share of the spoils.
Be there, sir.
In this pusat,
It's a gift from me to you.
be there.
Be there, sir.
Whenever you will conquer,
I'll come already.
I will come anytime.
Be there, sir.
Now it's time for Marmaracik
to explain the judge.
You all fought hard.
You have irrigated the whole country with your blood and sweat.
You may exist.
But...
who pays the greatest price,
He will manage Marmaracık.
Of course, price isn't everything.
But on a bad day,
the essence of man is revealed.
I see now.
You're all wondering what to say.
The name that will come out of my mouth,
it won't change anything for you.
that we are together,
only our banner
for us to move forward.
Because of this,
The ruler of Marmaracik...
Öktem Bey.
Goodbye, sir.
Since,
You have deemed me worthy of this sacred duty,
your trust is my legacy.
be there.
Games were built on it.
for your honour.
thrown on your name
You took a cue for the stain.
But...
yet you listened to the word of the brain.
Because of your stance
Marmaracik is your right.
I have an objection.
There is news from Bayındır Bey.
Like this.
Tell me, I said.
Mr. Osman,
We learned his new move.
He will attack Köprühisar.
You were right.
Osman does not stop.
But now we know his move.
Let's destroy it while we have it, Olof.
We will.
But first we have a job.
We're going to get Remus.
Mr. Osman!
In many conquests with you,
We gave many martyrs,
together.
Is Sade Öktem Bey lost?
You know me in your heart, Osman Bey.
I sacrificed everything for you.
Obama,
my alps, my lady.
If there is more, I will do it.
So it's not the throne, that's my point.
Not that...
The property that will be the headquarters in the conquest,
he conquered,
bloodshed,
It is the right of someone who has given blood.
for gas tomorrow,
with which face our valiants
We will call you, Osman Bey?
We will make new conquests, Turgut Bey.
Is it property effort?
that keeps us together
leave when there is no property.
Mr. Oktem,
His nephew Batur was martyred for Marmaracık.
without even experiencing the pain
was slandered.
Because of this,
because of his pain,
Marmaracik is his right.
The other sofa is finished.
Get the horses ready, Kutan.
It's your command, sir.
Mr. Turgut!
Oh, Mr. Turgut!
You chased us around,
From Marmaracik but...
What has the throne benefited us,
not you.
What an empty talk, you waste your breath,
Mr. Bayindir?
Are you chasing fitness?
Is the throne our concern?
Since it is not the throne,
what's up with this face?
Osman Bey,
Öktem considered the task appropriate.
It's up to us to say, may God bless you.
Is not it?
What will fall on me
don't worry, Mr. Bayindir.
If you say more,
I wouldn't say we are in the mansion of Mr.
get the news.
You teach right.
We are in the mansion of Mr.
If I mess with you now,
Mr. Bayindir,
He could not remove the task given to Mr. Öktem,
He made a grudge, they say.
Oh patience!
Oh, patience.
Patience.
Stay well.
Oh patience!
Come on Kutan, where are you?
Oh Alflower!
Do you come from oba or from physic?
come on,
I know what I will do to you.
Good luck, sir.
Thank you, thank you.
Thanks.
be present.
Sir!
girl!
Good news, I hope.
No, it is no.
You were so angry, you did,
Osman Bey, but...
Osman Bey became his principal again.
Marmaracik,
deserved us.
Informal Marmaracik is ours, babe.
Oh my god!
Will he find better than you?
Even though Osman is late,
He found a man to lean on.
Thank you babe, thank you.
But...
are these our eyes
I think they want to paint.
Why would they want to paint our eyes?
de and Max Inspirations we see
Osman's nephew
Aktemur...
Say it, come on.
of Alçiçek,
chasing after my daughter.
Subasi?
Ya babe, I'm bad too
I thought you were learning something.
That's good news, good.
Aktemur is a good boy.
Good boy, good boy.
If it will happen, let it be.
Mr. Oktem!
I say Aktemur is a good boy, girl.
Also,
Better than Osman Bey's nephew
Will we find a groom?
er?
Does our girl have a heart?
If you had waited a little longer,
I was going to stand on the ground like that tree, Subasi.
With the girl who doesn't have a heart in me,
Shall I come running to talk?
Since you were so reluctant,
if you hadn't come.
What did you come for?
Oh patience!
Oh patience, Alçiçek Hatun!
You called, you said it was important.
But obviously, what you did first
words are not enough
Let me call this Aktemur,
You said let me share some more.
It comes, after all.
Have a heart!
It will come again.
No,
not like that.
Now--
What's wrong, Alçiçek Hatun, what's wrong?
OK.
I don't have a heart.
OK, I'm not going to show up.
But don't do that.
My wound is very fresh.
It bleeds again every time you look at it,
don't you see
Don't look like that, I'll be a victim.
What do you want me to do, I don't understand.
What do I do?
Should I go from Yenişehir?
I can not go.
I have a duty.
I call him too.
You have a duty.
You have a duty, you have a mother.
I have my mother.
Out of all that...
You play games with me, Alçiçek.
I'm not going to allow this.
Aktemur!
Actemur?
Do you mean my name?
Do I hear right?
I couldn't throw off the earrings.
But I couldn't put it in my ear either.
I've been running around in my belt like that.
What does this mean?
Don't squint your eyes.
You shot me with them.
Don't withhold.
You have a heart too, huh?
Does that mean that?
There is, your eyes say.
I can also hear from your voice, heh.
What will change if I say I have a heart?
Once I said no,
the man who abandoned his love,
How will he make this difficult road?
I did not appear in your eyes,
Because I didn't see your face
Do you think I gave up?
Isn't love mine?
Even if it's not you, even if you don't have a heart,
my love with me.
with me
Even if my soul goes out
Even if my heart is soil, it is with me.
But...
You also have a heart.
This love
it is a blessing of heaven, Alçiçek Hatun.
You have a heart
is not it?
There is.
I have a heart, Aktemur.
Did it work?
But this road is very rough.
You left with a word.
On this difficult road,
How will you deal with my mother?
None of them is more difficult than being without you.
I'll deal with it all, me.
Even now I think of my mother.
If he sees us like this now,
do you know what happens?
Blood comes out.
Even if we get together
this wouldn't let us go.
We would be unhappy, Aktemur.
Once you pattern,
my name.
Pattern one more time!
We will be unhappy, I say.
What do you think?
We are also unhappy separately, Alçiçek Hatun.
Since both kinds
we will be unhappy
which I think...
we will be happy together.
But...
if you say so,
Why should we be unhappy separately?
Together,
together...
How is it going to be?
Robust,
open the map.
Sir, from Kartal Yuvası to Köprühisar,
to arrive,
This is the most secret way.
Is Cerkutay there too?
It's there as you ordered, sir.
Not just headquarters,
Also to Bilecik and Karacahisar
secret ways must be found.
But most importantly, Inegol.
You should come from İnegöl without being seen.
Turgut Bey also said,
He would instruct his alps to besiege.
In fact, he still has our catapults.
Where is Turgut Bey?
Hasn't it come yet?
We haven't heard from yet, sir.
Even though he knew we were going to explore.
or it's late
or it hasn't even set out yet.
We set off.
He who looks behind cannot see ahead.
Lets.
Now we continue the exploration.
You continue to explore.
Is there a destur, sir?
Come on, Kutan.
Mr. Osman,
Conquest of Köprühisar with the Alps
explored for.
The Alps await orders, too.
Aren't we going, sir?
Osman Bey didn't need us, Kutan.
Alhamdulillah, we are people of gas.
But we are always on the side of truth.
we are in favor
Now I see that
Mr. Osman,
He did not give the right to those who deserve it.
Back to back for years
the wardens he fought,
he didn't see.
In short, our value was not known, Kutan.
We also do not know our worth,
We make up for it by our absence.
So what are we going to do, sir?
Are we going to stand back from Cenk?
Don't you know Turgut Bey?
Just because we are not behind Osman Bey,
Are we going to back off from the gas?
This is the world
his neck is full of swear words.
You always have the Alps ready, Kutan.
We will certainly keep going.
It's your command, sir.
Ha Osman Bey,
without it.
Olof!
Remus, the Emperor's loyal commander!
olof.
The plays you translated with Kantakouzenos...
It's all out now.
Nothing is over yet.
Mr. Osman,
He will make Kantakouzenos talk.
The Emperor will learn everything.
And you...
Cantacuzenos,
We must save him.
Olof will also finish Osman's work.
Mother!
So girl, where are you?
If you hadn't come.
Well, your tent is not done, mother.
I just got out.
Come on, you rest, I'll take care of the counter.
what do you have?
What is this joy?
No.
What will it be, mother?
I heard about my father's mission.
Why are you surprised?
Would they find better than your father,
for that task?
Come on, don't distract me, I have work.
Ulgen Hatun.
I am Aktemur Bey.
What happens?
Come on, tell me.
What's going on, I saw you.
You were staring and staring.
Alçiçek has a heart for me too.
What did you say, sir, what did you say?
Destur!
Valide Ismihan Sultan!
They did not inform.
This arrival, you say no?
I don't know, Bala.
But after the conquest...
Anyways.
Let's say no, let's say no.
Come on, come on.
Quick!
Welcome, Ismihan Hatun.
You are welcome.
Osman Bey's ladies,
Malhun Hatun and Bala Hatun.
Where is Osman Bey?
to welcome us
He didn't bother, I guess.
Estagfurullah.
Osman Bey does not exist.
Had he known of your arrival,
He would have given you a worthy welcome, of course.
You came from the road, you are tired.
Let's get you to your room.
We did not come here to rest, Malhun Hatun.
Government jobs don't wait.
Of course it won't wait, Ismihan Hatun.
But in case the state does not wait for the job,
Osman Bey does not wait in the mansion.
It constantly adds new ones to its lands.
That's what I came for.
Osman Bey, while running from battle to battle,
your eye,
covered with fog.
where are you running to,
He couldn't see what he was destroying.
Someone has to stop him.
Now let's get to our main issue.
Where is Kantakouzenos?
Robust!
Just what they said
we saw it with our own eyes.
Köprühisar is well preserved.
But the obstacle that will intimidate the Turk,
has not yet been established.
Evalallah, sir.
Get over your sentence,
We will wave our banner.
Our work here is done.
Come on, Alps!
We will go to Yenişehir.
You exit.
who do not know the meaning of being a state,
he does not know his limits.
Where has he been seen, your great prince
that he is under arrest.
You are right.
With someone who thinks like this in this land
speaking, I was quite surprised.
Since I came
the hand I always extend as a friend,
I saw hostility.
Those times have passed,
cantacuzenos
Who are you, what do you want from me?
Al-i, Sultan of Seljuks,
Alaeddin's mother
I am Ismihan Sultan.
You too, heir to the Byzantine throne,
Give Kantakouzenos.
The name of Al-i Seljuk
reaches beyond its borders.
We have been acquainted with Byzantium for a long time.
We know each other very well.
we know.
The time has come, we have made peace.
The time has come, we fought.
Now is the time
It's deal time.
two states,
like Osman,
to the glory of the ignorant,
shouldn't be allowed.
Byzantine and Seljuk wars,
it was most beneficial for gentlemen like Osman.
As we got weaker, they got stronger.
Me,
imprison a Byzantine prince
they dared.
Let's give them the limit so that
Let's get stronger.
We will agree,
cantacuzenos
We will agree.
Now I have to get you out of here.
You're no use to me when I'm holding.
This was not good at all.
What will we do now?
I don't know, Bala.
But at a time like this,
We cannot contradict Ismihan Sultan.
Wait, where would you take it?
before you,
then the one holding the rope...
As long as you come to my land,
This will be the fate of all of you.
Cantacuzenos,
is free.
While Osman Bey was gone,
We cannot allow such a thing.
What you are saying is not correct.
Right and wrong to you
I'm not going to ask, honey.
take it away.
what you have given me,
especially your hospitality.
I will never forget.
until we meet again,
enjoy life.
Go to Tez Olof.
free of Kantakouzenos
You say you left.
Boran, bring Kantakouzenos to the sofa.
Storm!
Sir!
Kantakouzenos is not in the dungeon.
They released.
What do you say, Bala?
Who did this?
Who did?
Who released my prisoner?
Sultan of Konya, mother of Alaeddin,
Ismihan Sultan.
whoever you are
captive, my captive.
The city is my city.
Here, only my rule applies.
The one who lurks on my property,
I will rip your heart out.
Mr. Osman!
Know your limits.
Sultan of Konya,
as long as it's there
everything that is yours
it is ours.
If we pulled a coin,
It means we are on our property.
Do not even think about it!
Do not.
to reach out for what's mine
Don't get up, Ismihan Hatun.
Mr. Osman!
If you are Uc Bey,
You will bow to me.
No, if you say I am the state,
what is behind the sentence oba
will be taken away.
I said, 'Don't give me a hand.
You covet my obama,
girl!
He cuts the outstretched hand,
I'll cut out that eye.
Everyone will know.
I'll let you know if you don't know.
Here,
Mister is me too
The state is mine!